[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When does the vernal equinox occur in the Northern Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "March 20, 21, or 22", "incorrect_answers": ["September 20, 21, or 22", "December 20, 2, or 22", "June 20, 21, or 22"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term ethology, which refers to the study of animal behaviour, derives from a Greek word, which means what?", "correct_answer": "Custom", "incorrect_answers": ["Behaviour", "Life cycle", "Environment"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Lost Boys won only two awards. It won the Saturn Award for Best Horror Film and Corey Feldman won Best Young Actor in a Horror Motion Picture.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following happened to Tiny, a character from the movie House of 1000 Corpses?", "correct_answer": "His dad set the house on fire.", "incorrect_answers": ["His dad ran away.", "His dad killed him.", "His dad beat him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what body of water is the island of Malta located?", "correct_answer": "Mediterranean Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Pacific Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean", "North Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 45th Academy Awards in 1973, this 1972 movie received the prestigious Academy Award for Best Picture.", "correct_answer": "The Godfather", "incorrect_answers": ["Sounder", "Cabaret", "Deliverance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do you say hello in Russian?", "correct_answer": "Zdravstvuite", "incorrect_answers": ["Spasiba", "Dobry den", "Do svidanya"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was a common dish in England at the beginning of the century.  It contains raisins, sugar, chestnuts, rice, and 3 quarts of pork blood.", "correct_answer": "Blood Pudding", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver and lights", "Yule brod", "Blood Thirsty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of the tiger shark?", "correct_answer": "They give birth to live young.", "incorrect_answers": ["They can breath above water.", "They have eyelids.", "They have body hair."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The islands of the Pacific are collectively termed Oceania. Oceania is divided into several sub-groupings. In which of these is New Guinea located?", "correct_answer": "Melanesia", "incorrect_answers": ["Polynesia", "None of these", "Micronesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Rebels bomber in Star Wars?", "correct_answer": "Y-Wing", "incorrect_answers": ["Tie Bomber", "CIS Strike Bomber", "V-Wing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. President attempted to purchase Cuba from Spain?", "correct_answer": "Pierce", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnson", "Tyler", "Taylor"]}]